Good night.
We, Seino, Super Tough! Strong Energy! Positive Exciting Soul From Nagoya! Team Shachi!
We are now running this video in a hurry, but we would like to inform you about our one-man live concert
I have an important announcement about our one-man live concert "Kessen no shachimode" to be held at Tokyo Dome City Hall on January 4, 2025.
What a surprise, this Kessen no Shachimode!
We have been informed that it will be a "soul de magica"!
I don't know why.
Because it's on sale to the general public now!
Thankfully, arena seats and first floor seats have already been sold out!
Thank you very much!
We only have the 2nd and 3rd floor seats left.
I'm sure you'll all be at Tarmin...
We're so close, aren't we?
You did a great job, Killer Whale. - Yeah.
But that's a mistake. That's a mistake.
The Tokyo Dome City Hall is huge, so we can get in two or three times.
We actually had a few people from the daughters at the benefit,
Haru-chan wants to see it too, and so do the helpers. I was told that everything is going well,
I told them that's not true. I really want more and more people to see it.
I was thinking, "This is not good." I was happy to hear that, but I shared my impatience with the other members, and it grew,
So I asked them to make a video of it and show it to everyone.
It is not good to have a gap in perception.
We definitely want to make Tokyo Dome City Hall on January 8 a soul-destroying event.
I would like to express that desire here,
May I start with our history? There was a whole group, Team Shachihoko, and we changed our name to Team Killer Whale, right?
In 2018. Yes, we changed our name in 2018, and the staff changed completely at that time.
I see. We started to take on new challenges, such as Mikan's policy, and the new challenge of "Doubt Pop" and "Brass" at once,
We were challenging ourselves in many ways at the beginning of the name change,
I also learned about the harshness of the clarification process,
I also learned about the harshness of the challenges in the process of clarification, and I was determined to challenge myself and work even harder from here,
We worked on this project for one or two years through trial and error,
Gradually, people began to accept Team Shatch,
Then we started touring, and even had a sold-out show at LINE CUBE Shibuya,
Sold out. Yes, there was a national tour, and it was at LINE CUBE.
The next year was Shatchisama, Osaka? The next year will be Shatchisama, Osaka?
We were so close to the Corona Disaster that we finally came to the stage to meet Team Jas,
We were like, "Here we are at this stage,
We were forced to play a central role because we were entering the Corona Disaster at the very beginning of our week-long meeting.
It was frustrating.
It was very frustrating to not be able to do the gigs I really wanted to do because of the Corona disaster,
I was very frustrated that I couldn't show my happiness that I wanted to show,
And then, in the midst of such corona...
Then the next thing that became popular in the idol culture was the idea of being cute,
And we wanted to be cute idols. We wanted to be cute, you know.
You wanted to be cute, right?
You are cute!
You are totally cute!
They're cute!
She says everyone thinks so!
Thank you!
And, well, I've tried many things with cuteness,
We have been challenging ourselves in many ways, such as doing live performances in our home time, and in the Corona Disaster, we wanted to reach out to everyone,
So I've decided to take on various challenges.
I am very happy to have had the opportunity. And, I was able to take on many challenges,
And now that we are no longer restricted by the Corona, we can finally show the best of our new spirit in our live performances. We can finally show our new essence in our live performances!
That's right. We can finally show what we are now at this Tokyo Dome City Hall,
We can finally show you what we have been doing since 2018 at this Tokyo Dome City Hall,
It is very frustrating that we can't sell out the show at the Tokyo Dome City Hall.
Even though there are restrictions, the live show we did at Pacifico Yokohama, for example, was a great experience for us,
The Pacifico MISELTON was a place where we put together all the things we had fought for at the Corona Disaster and at the time of various clarifications,
I think that the Dome City Hall has something that can be delivered because of the current shirt with the addition of the cute,
That's what I meant by the title of this event.
That's why I chose the title "Kessen" for this event.
Also, although the Dome City Hall is the place where we have been thinking about our past, it is also the place where we will be able to showcase our dream of becoming a Japanese warrior.
But we also want to make our dream of a one-man live at the Nippon Budokan a success.
and to make it a success, this Dome City is absolutely indispensable.
this Dome City will be an absolutely indispensable point
It is an unchangeable fact that this Dome City is absolutely indispensable for the success of our dream Nippon Budokan.
I believe that it is absolutely essential for us, as well as for all of us, to be united with other members of the group.
That's why I want to accelerate the pace of our first live performance in 2025, and that's why I want to make it come true.
I hope this feeling reaches everyone.
I think the number of times we can take on a challenge is honestly limited.
But I think we are the ones who have been given various challenges.
The current story of our history and our private life are examples, but we have been allowed to change in many different ways,
I think this is a chance for me to pursue my dream,
I really think this is the chance for me to grab this dream, so please come to the Shirt Modes.
I hope that as many people as possible will come to this event.
Thank you very much.
We call this a battle that we cannot lose.
No one loses.
If you're thinking about coming now...
We want to make people who are thinking about coming want to go... just a little bit.
It's important to know what kind of show it's going to be.
Well, first of all, Nappy's done a lot of work on the costumes.
But this time I think it's a little too Haru.
Have you seen it?
Did you see it?
Yes, I did
It's so cute, isn't it? So cute!
The glamour of the show Larry's and...
I can't wait!
I can't wait to see it.
I can't wait to show it. I really want to see it.
The setlist and the contents are perfect for the beginning of the year,
The setlist and the contents are filled with the passion, happiness, and positivity of the orcas.
But in the past 13 years,
I hope that you will be able to enjoy the show and enjoy the show as much as I do.
Or someone who just recently fell in love with the show.
Or, on the other hand, someone who has been watching us for a long time.
No matter who you are, if you have been exposed to Killer Whales, you will never forget this song.
I'm sure there are many songs in this album that you will remember fondly.
I think the fusion of Team Killer Whale and Killer Whale is amazing.
There's a lot of stuff here.
On the other hand, for those who are coming to the show for the first time, there are many songs that will definitely stick with them.
Like nao said, it's like a grab bag.
That's really true.
It's full of surprises.
But, you know, the songs, I'm honestly confident that we can entertain you even if we don't all know the songs.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Honestly, I do.
That's the basic premise.
Even if you don't know the song, if you say something...
I'm confident that I can make you think it's fun even if you don't know the song.
So please don't think that you have to learn these songs or wonder which ones you have to listen to.
I don't think about what I have to listen to.
I don't think about what's fun.
I don't think about dancing.
There are things you can do, but you don't have to dance to them.
There are many ways to have fun.
I'm recommending it.
We encourage people to have fun in their own way.
It's really easy.
Like, "Let's go to the party.
We'd be happy if you could come as if you were going to a party.
Also, we'll randomly select
I'm going to give away
I'm going to give you a present of a live photo.
I've never been to a party before.
That's right.
That's why...
If you bring a friend, or a family member, or a friend, or a family member, or a family member, you can give them a gift.
So, please look forward to it, and please accept it, and please, please, please.
I know it's just information, but I've always been aware of Soul de Magica, and I'm sure you're all wondering how many more tickets are actually available.
I'm sure you're wondering how many tickets are actually left. I'm sure you are wondering how many tickets are actually left.
We are determined to sell out, so please let me tell you.
There are only 800 copies left!
Yes, we have 800 copies left. One month.
We know it's not easy to sell 800 copies in one month.
It's not easy to sell out in a month.
For 13 years.
I've been an idol for 13 years.
I know it's really difficult.
I'm confident that we will entertain you.
And I'm confident that we'll put on a show that you won't regret coming to.
I want as many people as possible to see our shows.
I want as many people as possible to see our dream
We want to sell out this battle of Shachimode.
Up until now, orcas have been
They've been very aggressive, like they want us to follow them, and they're the top killer whale downstream, so we've been trying to figure out what's going on.
We've had a lot of people following us, and we've always had the will to be strong so that they would follow us.
But I'd like to ask you again to do something for us.
Let's make Team Shachi...
We want to spread the goodness of Team SHACHI to as many people as possible, and we want to have a good time with you all.
Please help us!
We'd like to do whatever we can do in the remaining one month, and we'd also like to do our first live relay with the members.
We are going to do everything we can for the remaining one month, and we are also going to do a live relay for the first time. Please come and join us on January 4th at the Tokyo Dome City Hall Shachimode!
That's all for us!
Let's go!
Super Turn Strong Energy Positive Exciting Soul from Nagoya Team Shachi!
We'll be waiting for you!